snappytv.com 2013-12-30

# SnappyTV - Privacy

### Privacy Policy

Effective Date: February 9, 2011

At Afterlive.tv, DBA SnappyTV, (the "Company"), we respect your right to privacy and we understand that visitors to the Company’s site need to control the uses of their personal information. The privacy policy below details the measures taken by Company to protect your privacy in connection with your use of Snappytv.com and snappy.tv (the "Company Sites") and other related services provided by the Company (collectively, the “Service”).

#### A Note About Children

Children (i.e. those persons under the age of 13) are not eligible to use any of the Company Sites without supervision. We thus ask that children do not submit any information to us. If you are under the age of 13 and want to use any of the Company Sites, you may only do so under the supervision of your legal parents or guardians.

### When Does The Company Collect My Information, Including Personally Identifiable Information?

#### Registration.

When you register for a SnappyTV Account, the Company asks for your e-mail address, a user selected user name, and other information. Once you are a registered user you can update your profile and may be able to provide additional preferential information (e.g. website).

#### Browsing SnappyTV

You can watch videos on SnappyTV without having a SnappyTV Account. You also can contact us by e-mailing us directly without having to register for an account.

#### Your SnappyTV Account

For some activities on SnappyTV, like snapping a video and adding a comment, posting comments, and liking clips, you need a SnappyTV Account. We ask for some personal information when you create an account, including your e-mail address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access.

#### Usage Information

When you use SnappyTV, we may record information about your usage of the site, such as the channels and shows you snap, which other users you follow or who follow you, the videos you watch, your frequency of usage, elements you click on in SnappyTV (including UI elements and settings), and information you display about yourself. If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your SnappyTV Account.

#### Content You Disclose on the Site

Any personal information or comments that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g., video comments, your profile page) may be collected and used by others.

#### Special Contests or Promotions

The Company may occasionally present a special contest or promotion that is sponsored by another company. To qualify for entry in that contest or promotion, we may ask you to provide personal information. If we plan to share that information with the sponsor(s) or with others, we will provide a statement to that effect in the contest or promotion terms.

#### IP Address

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We will use your IP address to identify your geographic region in order to display the correct content for that region, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our site. Your IP address also may be used to gather broad demographic and geographic information for advertising and other purposes.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites. We use cookies to collect, store and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the services we provide. If you are a registered user, we will use a cookie to save your settings (such as, but not limited to, username and/or password) and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies are not enabled to allow third parties to access any of your personally identifiable information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit other websites you may be required to accept cookies. Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies.

#### Links to Other Sites

The Company Sites contain links to other websites. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. The Company Sites may also link to websites that feature Company trademarks and names along with trademarks and names of other companies. You should look at the privacy policy on that co-branded website, as the co-branded website may not be under Company’s control.

#### Information from Other Sources

For reasons such as improving user experience and providing customized communications to our users, the Company may receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information that we have received from you.

### How Is My Personally Identifiable Information Used By The Company?

#### Uses

If you submit personal information to SnappyTV, we may use that information to operate, maintain, and improve the features and functionality of SnappyTV, and to process any customer support activity or other communication you send to us.

We use cookies, web beacons, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit SnappyTV; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

#### Information That is Publicly Available

When you create a SnappyTV Account, some information about your SnappyTV Account and your account activity will be provided to other users of SnappyTV. Your SnappyTV Account name, not your e-mail address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on SnappyTV, such as when you snap videos or enter comments through SnappyTV. Other users can contact you by leaving a comment on the site. Any video clips and comments that you snap on SnappyTV may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by other SnappyTV users or the general public. You may also choose to add personal information which may include your name, gender, profile picture or other details, that will be visible to other users on your SnappyTV Profile page.

#### Your Choices

If you have a SnappyTV Account, you may update or correct your personal profile information, and other settings at any time by visiting your Settings page. You may control the information that is available to other users and confirm the people you’re following at any time by editing your SnappyTV People page. You may, of course, decline to submit personal information through SnappyTV, in which case you can still view videos and explore SnappyTV, but SnappyTV may not be able to provide certain services to you.

#### E-mail

We do not use your e-mail address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We may use your e-mail address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major SnappyTV changes or for customer service purposes). The e-mail may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the newsletters, including whether the e-mail was opened and/or what links (if any) were clicked. We will combine that information with other information we have about you and may use that information to improve your site experience and/or provide customized e-mail communications to you.

### Who Does the Company Share My Information With?

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us. We therefore do not sell, rent or give access to your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your prior consent, except as provided below.

The Company may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on the Company; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone’s safety.

The Company may share your information with certain third parties who provide services or products on the Company's behalf. For example, the Company may use third parties to perform functions on its behalf, like sending out and distributing the Company's administrative and promotional e-mails. The Company may share your personal information with such third party service providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal or e-mail, administer contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the the Company's websites and applications, troubleshoot, and provide customer service.

We may gather demographic information from you (for example, your age, education level or household income) from time to time. We will not share that information in a manner that identifies you as an individual with any other entity, unless we specifically ask for your permission at the time of collection of such data.

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets, and, depending upon the transaction, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. In the event that Company is acquired by another company, your personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party.

### Use Of Other Members - Information

As a user of the Service you will have access to other users’ personal information. You agree to use this information solely for sharing and communicating on the site. The Company and its users shall not tolerate spam of any kind. Accounts suspected of causing spam will be deleted immediately and such users shall not be allowed to register again. You are thus not permitted to contact any user of the Service via e-mail, marketing messages or other kinds of spam without receiving their prior consent. Please feel free to report any users you suspect of using the Service as a platform for spamming by contacting customer support.

### Security Measures

The Company has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These security measures include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems and maintenance of registration information in a secure database. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. We will protect the transmission of credit card information through industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. Please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our safeguards. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to SnappyTV or to any third party, and you do so at your own risk.

### Compromise of Personal Information

In the event that your personally identifiable information is compromised as a result of a known or suspected breach of security, the Company will attempt to notify you in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this privacy policy or as otherwise required by applicable law.

### Notification Procedures

It is the Company's policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business-related purposes, to the Company's users via e-mail notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Company Sites, as determined by the Company in its sole discretion.

### Acceptance of Privacy Policy

Your use of the Service, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and Company’s Terms of Service [http://www.snappytv.com/tos]. By using the Service, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Statement and those Terms of Service. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the top of this page to determine if the statement has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of the Service following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

### International Visitors

The Service is located within the United States. If you choose to use the Service from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, then please note that you are transferring your personally identifiable information outside of those regions to the United States for storage and processing. By providing your personally identifiable information on the Service you consent to that transfer, storage, and processing. Further, we may transfer this data from the United States to other jurisdictions in connection with storage and processing of data, fulfilling your requests, and operating the Service.

#### More Information

For questions concerning the Service or your account, please check out the Help page.

For more information about our privacy practices, write to us at:

SnappyTV Privacy

1153 Mission Street / San Francisco CA, 94103 / USA
